<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Xophie Moon</title>
    <link>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Xophie Moon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 19:41:50 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shipped</title>
      <link>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/shipped/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 19:41:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/shipped/</guid>
      <description>So I think I finally have my hands on HRT medication soon! I&amp;rsquo;ve got estradiol valerate tablets and aldactone coming in. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel that big but it&amp;rsquo;s hard to overstate how big this is for me. This is all I&amp;rsquo;ve ever wanted for so long. And it&amp;rsquo;s so close at hand!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pills</title>
      <link>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/pills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 20:55:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/pills/</guid>
      <description>It seems that Estradiol Valerate Depot Injection is not available easily in India. So I&amp;rsquo;ll have to make do with Spiro and Estradiol pills. It&amp;rsquo;s not illegal to buy drugs without a prescription here. It&amp;rsquo;s illegal to sell. But that&amp;rsquo;s none of my concern. So I do have a seller lined up and it&amp;rsquo;s going to be costlier than the injection. Since I can&amp;rsquo;t afford to stop in the middle if I can&amp;rsquo;t find the money to buy again or the seller runs out of stock, I am planning to stockpile for a few months and make sure I can have a steady stream for atleast a couple of months that way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Hormone Replacement Therapy</title>
      <link>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/starting-hrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 22:33:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/starting-hrt/</guid>
      <description>I am thinking of starting on hormones. I am going to self medicate because that&amp;rsquo;s honestly the easiest and most accessible option right now. I have no choice. Need to find the proper information. My starting off point is DIY HRT Wiki. The cheapest option is probably Estradiol valerate injection and spirolactone. I am struggling mentally because I am in no position right now to come out so I have to keep it hidden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Post</title>
      <link>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 18:30:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/test-post/</guid>
      <description>I won&amp;rsquo;t write anything here because it&amp;rsquo;s just a test deployment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toothache</title>
      <link>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/toothache/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 16:34:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/toothache/</guid>
      <description>Goddamn this toothache! It&amp;rsquo;s not even a cavity. It&amp;rsquo;s like there&amp;rsquo;s a direct highway between hell and the left side of my brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Tired</title>
      <link>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/so-tired/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 01:24:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/so-tired/</guid>
      <description>I am so tired. I need to sleep. But I need to write here. Something or the other. It&amp;rsquo;s sort of fun to write anything. Just random words alskfjlskjflkflskdjf. Hehe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Write</title>
      <link>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/what-to-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 20:18:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/what-to-write/</guid>
      <description>I have no idea what to write. So whenever I think that I have nothing to write, I&amp;rsquo;ll simply write that I have nothing to write. After all what I write doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to have any purpose. I don&amp;rsquo;t even know what the next sentence will be. Tuna sandwich tastes so good!
It seems like I just like to use blogs and especially static blog frameworks like Hugo to simply fiddle around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freedom of Self Expression</title>
      <link>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/freedom-of-self-expression/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 18:35:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/freedom-of-self-expression/</guid>
      <description>For me to write here continuously is difficult because I am afraid of expressing myself openly. I think for most people under normal circumstances they have little to hide. But this has never been the case for me. However, I now feel that since that is past and I do have a strong sense of being my own person now, I should express myself freely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Am I</title>
      <link>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/who-am-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 11:32:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/who-am-i/</guid>
      <description>I want to be Xophie Moon so badly. I feel like this is my identity but I cannot use it in my life because I haven&amp;rsquo;t come out yet. But I mustn&amp;rsquo;t fall into self pity. My dreams are close at hand and why shouldn&amp;rsquo;t I be Xophie Moon! Who determines who I am but me?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Just Write</title>
      <link>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/write-anything/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 10:43:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/write-anything/</guid>
      <description>I think I&amp;rsquo;ll just keep on writing whatever comes to my mind. Right now it&amp;rsquo;s that I am super casual about writing here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Moon</title>
      <link>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/welcome-to-the-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 08:47:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xophie.is-very.ga/y/posts/welcome-to-the-moon/</guid>
      <description>Hello! Welcome to my beautiful new website!
Have a nice day!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
